Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Subject Files, 1963-present UPG.RG.52
ULS Greensburg
- Programs [Dedication; Groundbreaking; Ribbon Cutting Ceremony], 1975-2012
  - Chambers Hall, June 20, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    See: Subject Files: Buildings -- Chambers Hall. For video cassette of ceremony renaming the Common Facilities Building, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, a.k.a. Student Center, see UPG.RG.60 VC 53 II.2.
  - Ferguson Carillon (The Edith Ferguson Chambers Carillon), September 8, 1995 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    See also UPG.RG.60 VC II. 1 for video cassette.
  - Ferguson Theater, November 13, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Friday, November 13, 1998
  - Humanities Academic Village [Humanities Village], October 13, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Joan Chambers Children's Collection, September 8, 1995 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    See also UPG.RG.60 VC II. 2 for video cassette.
  - Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Nature Trail, October 26, 1975 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Marsh Psychology Laboratory, April 17, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center. [Ground Breaking], December 6, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center, November 13, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Dedication Ceremony, Tuesday, November 13, 2007.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Buildings—Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center; See also UPG.RG.60 DVD8 for DVD of dedication ceremony.
  - Millstein Library (Fanny K. Millstein Library), May 5, 1995 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    See: Subject Files: Buildings -- Millstein Library. See also UPG.RG.60 VC II.5 for video cassette and UPG.RG.61 C8 for audio cassette.
  - Millstein Library, September 30, 2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony "Opening New Doors" Thursday, September 30, 2010.
    See also: UPG.RG.60 Prints -- Construction Projects, 2010.
  - Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village, January 9, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    "Village Hall". [later desginated Lyceum]. Memo dtd 1/9/01 From Mark McColloch To: UPG Community in re Ground Breaking Ceremony.
  - Outdoor Recreational Area, August 31, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Grand Opening
  - Rossetti House [Rossetti International House; Rossetti House for International Studies] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Science Building, 1974-1977 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [now called Smith Hall] Groundbreaking, June 5, 1974; Dedication, May 17, 1977. Commemorative Paperweight.
    See: UPG Archives UPG.RG.69 Artifacts.
  - Student Residence Hall Project, November 16, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    (Ground Breaking) (Phase I) [later designated Humanities Academic Village]
  - Tosatto Plaza and Tosatto Drive, June 27, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    See also UPG.RG.60 II. 6 for video cassette.
  - Westmoreland Hall, September 9, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
- Programs (Miscellaneous)
  For additional programs, See also: UPG.RG.52 Student Plays; UPG Performance Collective; UPG Players; UPG Theater Dept. Productions.
  - AACA [Antique Automobile Club of America] Eastern Division, May 26-28, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    National Spring Meet. May 26, 27, 28, 2005. [Saturday, May 28, Show Field at University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Campus.]
  - Andes Manta, Oct. 27, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Quintet from Ecuador Plays Vibrant Music of the Andes. [Poster, News Release.]
  - Andes Manta, A Concert of Andean Music, September 19, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ferguson Theater
    For video cassette see, UPG Archives UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Video Cassette VC VII.8a
  - "The Apocalypse" Art Show & Lecture, February 22, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    W.B. Yeats, A Second Coming. Village Hall, UPG
  - The Art of Business Theater, September 24, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Presented by Thomas Tierney. Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center
  - Broadway Battles Breast Cancer, October 28, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    A Benefit Concert for the Breast Cancer Research Foundation. Friday, October 28, [2011]. 7:30 p.m., UPG Campana Chapel. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. Sponsored by Performing Arts Society.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.60 DVD19. See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Broadway Battles Breast Cancer
  - Broadway Battles Breast Cancer Benefit Concert [The Performing Arts Society Presents...], October 20, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Campana Chapel
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Broadway Battles Breast Cancer
  - Chandalika, a Dance Drama in the Kuchipidi Style, October 7, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Choreographed and conducted by Padmabhushan Dr. Vempati Chinna Satyam. UPG, Ferguson Theater.
  - Drag Show [UPG Drag Show], October 11, 2017 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Pitt-Greensburg GSA and SAB Proudly Present: The First Annual UPG Drag Show. Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Hall.
  - East-Central American Society of Eighteenth-Century Studies, October 2-4, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    34th Annual Meeting. Oct. 2, 3, 4, 2003, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. Theme: Nature and Artistry. [Organizer: Dr. Sayre N. Greenfield, Assistant Prof. of English, Univ. of Pittsburgh at Greensburg.]
  - An Eclectic Evening of Radical One Act Plays!, November 21-22, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    The World Premier of The Cat Who Came Back and other international classics including: The Dumb Waiter, Taliban Pizza, and The Still Alarm!! [UPG Student Plays] Nov. 21, 22, 2003, UPG Ferguson Theater.
    See: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Student Plays
  - Egypt: Intersection of East and West, April 21, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Saturday, April 21, 2007. University of Pgh. at Greensburg. A Curriculum workshop in Greensburg, PA for secondary and tertiary educators interested in world cultures, religions, and languages; Western civilization or the Middle East, Africa, and African American history.
  - Fantasticks, The, November 15-16, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [n.b. UPG News Release dtd 10/28/85 in re a performance of The Fantasticks (book and lyrics by Tom Jones and songs by Harvey Schmidt), Nov. 15-16, Smith Hall, UPG Campus. Gives: cast members, director, stage manager, costume/make-up/props technician, pianist and instrumental accompanist/sound effects manager.]
  - Functioning Dysfunctional, May 16, 2013 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Written by Jesse Palatucci; Tech/Video Producer, Nathan LaSor; Songwriters for "Funny", Jesse Palatucci and Cody Kraski. Ferguson Theater [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg], May 16th, 2013. [A UPG Visual and Performance Arts Capstone Performance].
  - Grease, April 6-9, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Performing Arts Society Presents Grease: Book, Music and Lyrics by Jim Jacobs & Warren Casey. UPG Ferguson Theatre, April 6, 7, 8, 9 [2006].
    See also: UPG.RG.38 Ser.: Student Organizations--Performing Arts Society.
  - H-Bomb: Fission, Fusion, Fission. The drama of the Teller-Ulam dispute, September 28, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    by Helene Smith and Charles Haldane. A stage reading presented by the UPG Theatre Company.
  - Heinz Chapel Choir 2012 Spring Concert, April 21, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ferguson Theater, Pitt-Greensburg Campus [Sponsored by Pitt-Greensburg].
  - Immaculate Misconceptions, June 16-18, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    A Monologue Performance by Stephen A. Schrum, Special Musical Guest Jeremy dePrisco. June 16 and 18, 2006, 8 p.m. Ferguson Theater, UPG Campus.
    See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 2 for a DVD of the performance of Immaculate Misconceptions (V11.DVD.2); See: UPG.RG.61 for Cd "Immaculate Misconceptions music by Jeremy dePrisco from the play by Stephen Schrum." Blue Buddha Records BLBU5 c2006 Jeremy dePrisco. See also: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File--Schrum, Dr. Stephen and dePrisco, Jeremy.
  - Indian Classical Dancing in the Odissi Style by Sharon Lowen, November 4, 1991 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    UPG, Smith Hall
    For UPG News Release, See: UPG.RG.27, News Release, Oct. 22, 1992; for videocassette of performance, See: UPG.RG.60 VC VII.1.
  - Indian Classical Dancing in the Kuchipudi Style by Kamala Reddy, November 8, 1991 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    UPG, Smith Hall Auditorium. Sponsored by the Performing Arts Society of UPG.
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, March 20, 1991 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    UPG, Smith Hall. Performed by Vishwa Mohan Bhatt on the Guitar and Sukhvindar Singh on the Tabla. Presented by Music Club of UPG.
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, October 19, 1994 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    UPG, Wagner Dining Hall. Artists: Rajeeb Chakraborry (sarod), and Reena Schrivastava (sitar) with tabla accompaniment by Kousic Sen.
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, March 31, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Wednesday, March 31, 1999 [memo in re concert]
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, March 29, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ferguson Theatre, Thursday, Mar. 29, 2001, 7:30 p.m. The Artistes: Tejendra Majumdar (sarod); Subhankar Banerjee (tabla).
    For photos, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Indian Classical Music Concert. For video cassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Video Cassettes VC VII.12
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, October 22, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ferguson Theater, Tuesday, Oct. 22, 2002, 7:30 p.m. The Artistes: Purbayan (sitar), Abhijit Banerjee (tabla).
    For videocassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Videocassette VC VII.7; for program, see UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Programs (Miscellaneous); for sound recording, see UPG.RG.61 Cassette C.12.
  - Indian Classical Music Concert, October 21, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ferguson Theater, Oct. 21, 2003, 7:30 p.m. Artists: Ken Zuckerman, an American who directs the Ali Akbar College in Basel Switzerland; Aninda Chatterjee, an eminent tabla player from India. [Announcement by Manhar Vyas, 11/9/03]
    For videocassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Videocassettes VC VII.20.
  - The International Club of University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Presents An Evening of Arias and Songs, April 10, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Soprano, Priya Palekar Accompanied by Sean Kelly on the Piano. Ferguson Theater
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight, February 18, 1990 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    arranged and directed by Vernell A. Lillie. [program presented in UPG Smith Hall auditorium, 7:00 p.m.]
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents The Buffalo Soldiers Plus One, February 17, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    program presented in UPG Ferguson Theater
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents Bubbling Brown Sugar, February 15, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [program presented at UPG Ferguson Theater, Tuesday, Feb. 15, 2005]
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents Mahalia Jackson: Standing on Holy Ground, February 15, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [program presented at UPG Ferguson Theater]
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents Sarafina!, February 20, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [program presented at UPG Ferguson Theater, Tuesday, Feb. 20, 2007.]
  - Kuntu Repertory Theatre presents The House That Carol Built, April 1, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [program presented at UPG Ferguson Theater, Sunday, April 1, 2012]
  - Monologues, The, April 10, 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [News Release Apr. 8, 2019]
  - PAS Slovak Folk Dance Ensemble, February 28, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Ferguson Theater. Thursday, February 28, 2002, 7:30 p.m.
  - Senior Citizens Expo 2006 [Senator Bob Regola's Senior Citizens Expo 2006] Guide to Exhibitors, May 11, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    UPG Chambers Hall, May 11, 2006, 10 a.m. to 1 p.m.
  - Senior Recognition Ceremony, May 9, 1987 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg.
    See: UPG.RG.39.1 Ser.: Subject Files--Miscellaneous Subjects.
  - She Sings: An Evening of Music & Art Benefiting Blackburn Center, 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [2nd Annual]
  - Sigma Tau Delta Presents "Evermore..." "An Evening with Poe", October 26, 1990 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [Lectures: "Poe: The Myth and the Man" by Dr. Donald Reilly; "The Unity of Poe's Chaotic Universe" by Dr. Richard Blevins; Reading of Poe's Poetry by Prof. Gary Lutz]
  - [Sigma Tau Delta Presents] Readings from the Mist...An Evening with Celtic Authors, March 1, 1991 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Presentations: Greta Regitz, "The Significance of the Written Word"; Bonnie Chambers, "The Influence of Ancient Religions on W.B. Yeats"; Dr. Richard Blevins, "A Presentation of Helen Adam".
  - Sigma Tau Delta presents The Bone Fire, 1992-1993? (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Sigma Tau Delta. Spring Initiation and Poetry Reading, April 11, 1994 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Sol y Canto: Celebrating the Roots of Latin American Music, October 5, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. 8:00 p.m. Friday, October 5, 2007
  - Sure Thing by David Ive and An Actor's Nightmare by Christopher Durang, November 30-December 1, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Brought to you by affiliates and students of UPG at Ferguson Theatre, Thursday, November 30, Friday, December 1 [2000], 8:00 p.m.
    See: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Student Plays (For video cassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Video Cassettes VC VII.13)
  - Sigma Tau Delta. Spring Initiation and Poetry Reading, April 11, 1994 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Sol y Canto: Celebrating the Roots of Latin American Music, October 5, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Sure Thing by David Ive and An Actor's Nightmare by Christopher Durang, November 30-December 1, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Tuna, La, April 3, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [performance at UPG April 3, 2002]
  - Tuna, La, April 14, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [performance at UPG April 14, 2003]
    [For videocassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Videocassette VC VII.18]
  - [UPG] Performing Arts Society presents Godspell, March 25-26, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  - Vagina Monologues, The, February 15-17, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [UPG] Gender Issues Group & Sigma Tau Delta Present...UPG Ferguson Theatre.
  - Vagina Monologues, The, February 9-10, 2017 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    [Program of performance, Campana Chapel and Lecture Center, UPG, sponsored by the Gay-Straight Alliance.]
  - Voices of the Desert: Victims of Saddam Hussein Finally Speak, January 9, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Monday, January 9, 2006, Ferguson Theater, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. [In 2005, a team of experts--including Robert Bytheway, Dr. Joan Bytheway, and Dr. Victor Weedn--traveled to Baghdad to exhume, examine, and preserve human remains from two mass graves in Iraq. Program included presentations by two Iraqi Americans: Anthony Carmeni and Reem Carmeni.]
  - Waking, A. A One Act Play, November 9-10, 2013 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    by Meg Hughes, Directed by Karen Ricco. Nov. 9, 2013, 7:30 PM, 28 West Second Gallery & Studio Space; Nov. 10, 2013 at 2:30 PM Pitt-Greensburg Campana Chapel. Sponsored by: Performing Arts Society & Delta Psi Omega. Funded by: Student Government Association.
- Public Policy Major (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
- Quest...Finding Your Future, 2009-2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
  2009 2010 2011 2012 2013 2014 2015 2016
- Quilt [UPG Quilt], 2001-2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5, Cabinet 1)
  First quilt, "UPG Beginnings", completed in 2001. Covers the tenure of the first President of UPG, Dr. Albert B. Smith, 1962-1980. Quilters: Dolly Biskup, Beth (Mrs. Frank) Cassell, Pat Duck, Jennifer Fetter, Karen Gavula, Mary Louise Hill, Joyce (Mrs. Carl) Rossman, Clara Vana, Nancy Young.
  Second quilt, "Building UPG", completed in 2003. Covers the tenure of the second President of UPG, Dr. George F. Chambers, 1980-1997. Quilters: Dolly Biskup, Joyce Bucchi, Sandy Buehner, Beth (Mrs. Frank) Cassell, Marion Chambers, Pat Duck, Jennifer Fetter, Mary Louise Hill, Hollie Ramaley (student), Joyce (Mrs. Carl) Rossman.
  Third quilt, "40th Anniversary", completed in 2004. "The quilters, a volunteer group of faculty, staff and students created this quilt in honor of UPG's 40th Anniversary. Quilt consists of autographed signature patches of the various constituencies of the campus community."
  For photos of the 1st and 2nd quilts, See UPG.RG.60 Visual Images -- Prints -- Quilts. See also Oversize Prints.
  Quilts are physically stored in UPG.RG.69 Artifacts [Textile & Fabric Storage Box]
- Radio Station [UPG Radio Station] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  See also: UPG.RG.38 Ser.: Student Organizations. Radio Station Club.
- "Read for Lifelong Learning" Program, 1998-1999 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  1998/1999 pilot year. Sponsored by the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Chapter of the SPEA (Student Pennsylvania State Education Association).
  For photographs, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images -- PR (prints).
- Resident Assistants [RA'S; UPG RA'S], 1996-2011 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  See also: Over size prints: UPG.qRG.60 Prints. Resident Assistants 2007-2008
  List of RA's at UPG 1996/97-2010/11
- Residents of the Month, 2014-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  2014, Sept.-Nov. 2015, Jan.-Mar., Sept.-Nov. 2016, Jan., Feb., Mar., Oct. 2017, Jan., Mar., Oct. 2018, Sept., Oct. 2019, Jan., Feb., March, Sept., Oct. 2020, Jan.
- Rose Trophy, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  Inaugurated in 2004. The Rose Trophy is an all-sports trophy that will travel between the two campuses of UPG and UPBradford. The "host" of the trophy will be determined by the winner of the overall sports competition between the two campuses. The trophy is named for Dr. M. Richard Rose who, as an assistant to the Vice-Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, had the responsibility for the academic and physical creation of three of the University's regional campuses, including Pitt-Greensburg, Pitt-Bradford and Pitt-Titusville.
- Rossetti House [Rossetti International House; Rossetti House for International Studies] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  [now called: International Academic Village] Includes: dedication program, program schedules, news releases, news clippings, publicity posters for events.
- ROTC [Pitt-Greensburg Army ROTC] Scholars in Service Program [Americorp Scholars in Service Program], 2005-2007 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  General File 2005- File contains, et. al., documentation of the commissioning of Michael Austin Wright as a Second Lieutenant in the U.S. Army and who was the first officer commissioned from the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg ROTC program. May 1, 2007.
- Salute Veterans Honor Society, April 9, 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  Induction and Graduation Social
- Scholarships [UPG Scholarships] [Awards], 2006-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  Includes: Program of the "Inaugural Donor Scholarship Luncheon and Program", Thursday Mar. 30, 2006, Hempfield Room, Chambers Hall; Invitation and Program, Second Annual Donor Scholarship Luncheon, Thursday, March 29, 2007. 2007 Program gives 2006-2007 Named Scholarship Recipients. [Gives a list of Scholarships available at Pitt-Greensburg, when they were established, criteria for obtaining them, and an explanation of why they were established. Also, includes list of Endowments and upcoming scholarships.] Program, Third Annual Donor Scholarship Luncheon, Thursday, April 3, 2008. 2008 Program gives 2007-2008 Named Scholarship recipients. [Gives a list of scholarships available at UPG, when they were established, criteria for obtaining them, and an explanation of why they were established.]; Ruth L. M. Kuschmierz Endowed Fund in Support of German Language, Literature and Culture (2014); Joel D. Sabadasz Striving for Excellence Endowment Fund (2014); Nancy Florez-Estrada Menoring and Leadership Award for Students (2015); news release dtd 1/4/16, "Pitt-Greensburg announces Full-Tuition Scholarship Competition through Feb. 5 [2016]."; [Student Resource Funds Scholarships 2002-2010..]; [News Release 10/5/2018] "Top High School Students Encouraged to Enter Full-Tuition Scholarship Competition" [3 $50,000 4 year scholarships: Lilliana Duff, Hunter Fishell, Mckenzie Huntebrinker]; Kerry W. Holzworth Biology Endowment [2019?].[News Release 11/21/2019] "Science Scholarship Showdown... high school students compete against each other for scholarships.]
- Senior of the Year [UPG Senior of the Year], 1998-2017 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  Award presented at the Honors Convocation.
  1998 Roslyn Ciacco 1999 Gina Giallonardo 2000 Romy Shinn 2001 Jana Giallonardo 2002 Erin O'Donovan 2003 Mitchell Paterline 2004 Brian Root 2005 Kristen Verenna 2006 Jihan Allay 2007 Jason Downey 2008 Melissa Wojtaszek 2009 Diane Williams 2010 Jennifer Komenda 2011 Kate Sadler 2012 John Paul ("JP") Hilzendeger 2013 Zachary Weisner 2014 Scott Szypulski 2015 Emily Stark 2016 Noel Saraceno 2017 Tara Ritenour
- Senior Week, 2009 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  1st Annual
- Smart Growth Partnership of Westmoreland County (SGPWC) (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
- Snowflake Ball (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  For photographs See Also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Snowflake Ball UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Negatives
- SOPA hoops Saturday [Special Olympics Pennsylvania of Westmoreland County] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
- Speed Interviewing (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
- Spring Carnival (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  For photographs See Also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Spring Carnival Visual Images--Negatives
- Spring Fling (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
  For photographs See Also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Spring Fling Visual Images--Negatives
- Spring Week (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 6)
- State of the Campus, Convocation on the, 2001-2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  First such convocation at the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Sept. 14, 2001.
  2001, Sept. 14. [Includes Program; President's Report to the Community, 2000-2001; University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Campus Agenda, 2001-2002]
  2002, Sept. 6 [Includes University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Campus Agenda 2002-2003] 2003 Convocation cancelled. File contains: the text of the address which would have been given by Dr. Cassell at the State of the Campus Convocation. File also includes a copy of the 7th, [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg] Annual Agenda 2003-2004 and a copy of the President's Report to the Community 2002-2003.
  Sept. 13, 2010. See: UPG.RG.02.5 President. Smith, Dr. Sharon P. Ser.: Documents. Sept. 12, 2011. See: UPG.RG.02.5 President. Smith, Dr. Sharon P. Ser.: Documents.
- Strengthening Institutions Program (SIP) (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- Student Plays [Student One Act Plays; University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Workshop], 2000-2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)